Chatman, Abraham Collection of the Rochester Joint Board, ACWA News Clippings and Photographs 6408
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Abraham Chatman Collection of the Rochester Joint Board, ACWA News Clippings and Photographs
1930-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Chatman, Abraham D.
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA)
10/1/2015Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Rochester Joint Board.
6408
4.33 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
News clippings, photographs.
9200844
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 14, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 24, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
9200844
- Forward - vol. L, no.17,736 (July 13, 1946) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Times-Union, Rochester - Broadside/Poster - (Saturday, June 19, 1982) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Abraham Chatman Portrait (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Keogh (1983) - (contains the Amalgamated Song Book and 8 photographs (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Standard-Times - New Bedford, Mass. (Friday, August 18, 1967) - also contains 5 photographs (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Labor and Culture (Fall, 1941) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Tenth Biennial Convention of the AMCWA (1930-1934) (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Proceedings and Executive Council Reports of the AFL-CIO (Nov. 15-20, 1979) (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Clippings - Scrapbook on the ILG Fight, 1947, collected by Abraham D. Chatman, Manager of the Rochester Joint Board, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Scrapbook of news clippings, 1937-1940 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Scrapbook of clippings covering the period from the early 1930's to 1951 and chiefly devoted to the activities of the Rochester Joint Board, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America collected by Abraham D. Chatman, Manager of the Rochester Joint Board, 1930-1951 (Box 1, Folder 11)